

REYNALDO R. DALOG

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

#48 MABINI ST., DISTRICT 1, CAUAYAN CITY ISABELA, PHILIPPINES 3305

AVAILABILITY: I CAN START FOR WORK AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.

CONTACT

+639213903864

http://reynaldodalog.com va.reynaldodalog@gmail.com www.facebook.com/reynaldodalog

EDUCATION

Isabela State University
BS - Information Technology

Jun 2003 - Apr 2007

SKILLS

Graphic Design
Illustrator
Web Design
Web Development
Color Theory
Video Editing
Web Server Administration

ABOUT ME

I have 10 years of working experience as an I.T professional. I have a considerable amount of experience in computer hardware. I also have been exposed in various software applications such as Photoshop, illustrator, Canva, Affinity Designer and Wordpress for Web Designing.

In the years I have been working I gained and mastered numerous skills such as configuring computer system and network, and Graphic and multimedia designing.

EXPERIENCE

Website Designer

Jan 2020- Present

MML Digital Marketing

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients, Working with different content management systems, Communicating design ideas using user flows, process flows, site maps and wireframes, Incorporating functionalities and features into websites, Designing sample pages including colors and fonts, Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure.

Website Developer

QRX Digital

February 2020 - May 2020

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.

Freelance Web - Graphic Designer

Virtualahan

Apr 2018 - May 2020

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.

System - Administrator

Cauayan Medical Specialists Hospital

June 2013 - April 2018

Maintain and Troubleshoot Computer System and local Network, Develop Hospital Website, Install and update Hospital Information System, Troubleshoot and Install Computer Hardware and Software, Design Graphic and Media Materials, Always Securing Back up and Restoration process every 3 hours operation.

EDUCATIONAL ATTAINMENT

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

College

Isabela State University – Cauayan Campus San Fermin Cauayan City, Isabela Jun 2003 - Apr 2007

High School

Isabela Colleges Cauayan City, Isabela (1999 – 2003)

Elementary

Cauayan South Central School Cauayan City, Isabela (1990 – 1996)

CERTIFICATION

Virtualahan

Wordpress Masterclass - Elementor Setup Aug 2020

UDEMY

HTML and CSS for Beginners - Build a Website & Launch ONLINE Sept. 24, 2020

UDEMY

Learn Responsive Web Development from Scratch Oct 02, 2020

UDEMY

Complete Wordpress Theme Development Course Feb 27, 2021

SEMINARS ATTENDED

3rd Bizbox IT-Summit

Bayanihan Center Hall A.Pioneer St., Pasig, Metro Manila Jan 24, 2017

CCNA Collaboration Voice Over IP and Video

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

CCNA Security ASA Firewall VPN and GRE Tunneling

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

Windows Server 2012 Clustering and Windows Deployment Services

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

VMWare Sphere and vCloud Director

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

REFERENCES:

Raquel J. Gammad

Acting Branch Head Producers Savings Bank Corporation

Tel.No.: +639956455835

 ${\bf Email: raquel.gammad@producersbank.com.ph}$

Relationship: client

Aldrin G. Coloma

Chief Executive Officer Latreia Prime Solution

LEI Partners LLC / Truckload Logistics

Tel.No.: Phil: +639776284625 USA: +17047544325

Email: aldrincoloma7@gmail.com acoloma@leipartners.net

Relationship: Client